[
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: It's been an hour and not one of Speaker 1's classmates has shown up! Speaker 1 tell you, when Speaker 1 actually die some people are gonna get seriously haunted!",
      "Speaker 2: There you go! Someone caSpeaker 2!",
      "Speaker 1: Ok, ok! Speaker 1'm gonna go hide! Oh, this is so exciting, Speaker 1's first mourner!",
      "Speaker 3: Hi, glad you could coSpeaker 3.",
      "Speaker 2: Please, come in.",
      "Speaker 4: Hi, you're Chandler Bing, right? Speaker 4'm Tom Gordon, Speaker 4 was in your class.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh yes, yes... let Speaker 2... take your coat.",
      "Speaker 4: Thanks... uh... Speaker 4 so sorry about Ross, it's...",
      "Speaker 2: At least Ross died doing what Ross loved... watching blimps.",
      "Speaker 1: Who is Ross?",
      "Speaker 2: Some guy, Tom Gordon.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 don't remember Ross, but then again Speaker 1 touched so many lives.",
      "Speaker 3: So, did you know Ross well?",
      "Speaker 4: Oh, actually Speaker 4 barely knew Ross. Yeah, Speaker 4 came because Speaker 4 heard Chandler's news. D'you know if Ross's seeing anyone?",
      "Speaker 3: Yes, Ross is. Speaker 3.",
      "Speaker 4: What? You... You... Oh! Can Speaker 4 ask you a personal question? Ho-how do you shave your beard so close?",
      "Speaker 2: Ok Tommy, that's enough mourning for Tommy! Here we go, bye bye!!",
      "Speaker 4: Hey, listen. Call Speaker 4.",
      "Speaker 2: Ok!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Chandler Bing",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 4",
        "rid": [
          4
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alumni"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "Tom Gordon",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          4,
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alumni",
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "",
          "call me"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "Tommy",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Tommy",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: So, eh... it's probably gonna be hard for you to leave Boston, huh?",
      "Speaker 2: Actually, Speaker 2'm kinda happy to be leaving... Speaker 2 just broke up with someone.",
      "Speaker 1: Ooh... so sad... Still, it can't be easy for you to leave Harvard? Especially after working alongside a Nobel Prize winner like Albert Wintermeyer?",
      "Speaker 2: Actually, Alby is the guy Speaker 2 broke up with.",
      "Speaker 1: You... you dated Albert Wintermeyer?",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah...",
      "Speaker 1: ... And you called Albert Wintermeyer Alby!? Speaker 1 mean that's like... like calling Albert Einstein... er... Alby...",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah, well, Alby...",
      " is a brilliant man.",
      "Speaker 1: Eh, you think? Speaker 1 mean, you went out with a guy who improved the accuracy of radiocarbon dating by a factor of 10!",
      "Speaker 2: Yes! And while that is everything one looks for in a boyfriend, Alby...",
      " had a lot of issues...",
      "Speaker 1: Oh! like what?! Oh Speaker 1'm sorry, Speaker 1 don't mean to pry... it's just that this must be what regular people experience when regular people watch \"Access Hollywood\".",
      "Speaker 2: Ok, you want the dirt? Alby was seriously insecure. Speaker 2 mean, Alby was really intimidated by the guy Speaker 2 dated before Alby.",
      "Speaker 1: Who is intimidating to a guy who won the Nobel Prize?",
      "Speaker 2: A guy who won two.",
      "Speaker 1: Two? Wha...? Don't tell Speaker 1 you dated Benjamin Hobart",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah... for three years.",
      "Speaker 1: Oh Speaker 1's God! Have you ever been in a relationship with someone who hasn't won the Nobel Prize?",
      "Speaker 2: ... no... bu but there was Speaker 2's first boyfriend Billy.",
      "Speaker 1: Oh yeah? no, no Nobel Prizes for Speaker 2's first boyfriend Billy?",
      "Speaker 2: No, but Speaker 2's first boyfriend Billy did just win the McArthur genius grant.",
      "Speaker 1: Huh... huh... what a loser! Some more wine?"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Boston",
        "rid": [
          18
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:place_of_residence"
        ],
        "t": [
          "leave"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "GPE"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Harvard",
        "rid": [
          22
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:employee_or_member_of"
        ],
        "t": [
          "leave"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Albert Wintermeyer",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "broke up with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Benjamin Hobart",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "relationship"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Billy",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "first boyfriend"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Albert Wintermeyer",
        "y": "Nobel Prize winner",
        "rid": [
          29
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:title"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Albert Wintermeyer",
        "y": "Alby",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Albert Wintermeyer",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "broke up with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Albert Wintermeyer",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "man",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "loser",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Billy",
        "y": "a loser",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Billy",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "first boyfriend"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Boston",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          32
        ],
        "r": [
          "gpe:residents_of_place"
        ],
        "t": [
          "leave"
        ],
        "x_type": "GPE",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Benjamin Hobart",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "relationship"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Harvard",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          35
        ],
        "r": [
          "org:employees_or_members"
        ],
        "t": [
          "leave"
        ],
        "x_type": "ORG",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hi!",
      "Speaker 2: Hi!",
      "Speaker 1: So umm, what's this book about?",
      "Speaker 2: You didn't read this one either?!",
      "Speaker 1: Well, Speaker 1 was gonna, but Speaker 1 accidentally read something else.",
      "Speaker 2: What?",
      "Speaker 1: Vogue! Hey, so tell Speaker 1 about this Jane Eyre woman.",
      "Speaker 2: No! You should've read it yourself!",
      "Speaker 1: Come on Phoebe! Don't be such a goodie-goodie!",
      "Speaker 2: Fine! Okay, all right, so Jane Eyre, first of all, you'd think Jane Eyre's a woman, but Jane Eyre's not. Jane Eyre's a cyborg.",
      "Speaker 1: A cyborg?! Isn't that like a robot?!",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah, this book was light years ahead of this book tiSpeaker 2.",
      "Speaker 3: Sorry Speaker 3'm late. Let's get started. So, what did everybody think about Jane Eyre?",
      "Speaker 2: Umm, Rachel and Speaker 2 were just discussing it and Jane Eyre had some very interesting insights.",
      "Speaker 3: Well, go ahead Rachel.",
      "Speaker 1: Uh, thank you Phoebe. Umm, well, what struck Speaker 1 most when reading Jane Eyre was uh, how this book was so ahead of this book tiSpeaker 1.",
      "Speaker 3: If you're talking about feminism, Speaker 3 think you're right.",
      "Speaker 1: Yeah, well, feminism yes, but also the robots."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "goodie-goodie",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hi.",
      "Speaker 2: Hi.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 just finished getting Phoebe all dressed to meet Mike's parents. getting Phoebe all dressed to meet Mike's parents's so nervous, it's so sweet!",
      "Speaker 2: Guess what? Speaker 2 made Emma laugh today.",
      "Speaker 1: You WHAT? And Speaker 1 missed it? Because Speaker 1 was giving a makeover to that stupid hippie?",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah, and it was uhm... it was like a real little person laugh too. It was... it was like uhm... Only... only not creepy.",
      "Speaker 1: Well... well, what did you do to make her laugh?",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 uhm... Well, Speaker 2 sang... well actually Speaker 2 rapped... Baby Got Back...",
      "Speaker 1: You WHAT? You sang... to our baby daughter... a song about a guy who likes to have sex with women with giant asses?",
      "Speaker 2: But you know what, if you think about it, it actually promotes a healthy uhm... body image... because... even big butts or uhm... juicy doubles.",
      "Speaker 1: owwwww...",
      "Speaker 2: Please don't take our baby daughter away from Speaker 2!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Phoebe",
        "y": "Mike",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Phoebe",
        "y": "stupid hippie",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Mike",
        "y": "Phoebe",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Emma",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "baby daughter"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Baby",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Emma",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "baby daughter"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Baby",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Emma",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "baby daughter"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Emma",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "baby daughter"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Emma",
        "y": "Baby Got Back",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "laugh"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: 'Okay. Okay, daddy we'll see you tomorrow night. Okay bye-bye.'",
      "Speaker 2: We?",
      "Speaker 1: Are ah, having dinner with Speaker 1's Dad tomorrow night, Speaker 1 hope that's okay.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh shoot, tomorrow's not so good, Speaker 2'm supposed to um, fall off the Empire State building and land on a bicycle with no seat. Sorry.",
      "Speaker 1: Ross, Speaker 1's father doesn't hate you.",
      "Speaker 2: Please, Speaker 1's father refers to Speaker 2 as 'wethead'.",
      "Speaker 1: But honey Speaker 1's father calls everybody by a nicknaSpeaker 1! Okay, look, Speaker 1 know, all right, just one dinner, please, just one night for Speaker 1, please. Speaker 1 just want Speaker 1's father to love you like Speaker 1 do."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "wethead",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          "nickname"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "honey",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "daddy",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          1,
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression",
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "love",
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "honey",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hey Pheebs.",
      "Speaker 2: Hey!",
      "Speaker 1: Any sign of your brother?",
      "Speaker 2: No, but your brother's always late.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 thought you only met your brother once?",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah, Speaker 2 did. Speaker 2 think it sounds y'know big sistery, y'know, 'Frank's always late.'",
      "Speaker 1: Well relax, your brother'll be here."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Pheebs",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Frank",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          "brother"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Frank",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          "brother"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Pheebs",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Monica.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh Speaker 2's God! He just said Speaker 2's naSpeaker 2! Did you hear that?",
      "Speaker 1: Monica bang!",
      "Speaker 3: Okay, Speaker 3 heard that.",
      "Speaker 2: Did Speaker 2 just say 'Monica bang'?",
      "Speaker 3: Uh-huh.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh Speaker 2's God! Speaker 2's gonna rat Speaker 2 out!",
      "Speaker 1: Monica bang!",
      "Speaker 2: Oh-ho-ho, sweetie, sweetie, you gotta stop saying that, now. It's no big deal, it's not even worth mentioning, you see we all do it all the tiSpeaker 2. See watch this, Ben, Ben, Ben. Ow, Monica bang! Ben bang. Ben bang. Ben bang. Bang, Rachel bang! Oh, isn't that fun?",
      "Speaker 3:  Look at that! Look at that! We all do it. Okay, Speaker 3'm stopping now.",
      "Speaker 2: You okay?",
      "Speaker 3: Oh yeah! Y'know, if it's not a headboard, it's just not worth it's not a headboard."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Monica bang",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "sweetie",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "sweetie",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Rachel bang",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "sweetie",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Oh hey! Wait up!",
      "Speaker 2: Hi!",
      "Speaker 1: Congratulations! Speaker 1 didn't want to say anything in front of Joey because Speaker 1 didn't know if Joey knew yet.",
      "Speaker 2: What, that we had a baby? Come on letwe give Joey a little credit, although Joey did eat a piece of plastic fruit earlier.",
      "Speaker 1: No! No, that you and Rachel are engaged!",
      "Speaker 2: What?",
      "Speaker 1: Oh, it's a secret. Oh goodie! Yes! We haven't done the secret thing in a long tiSpeaker 1.",
      "Speaker 2: Phoebe, there is no secret. Okay? Speaker 2 didn't propose.",
      "Speaker 1: Are you lying? Is this like that time you tried to convince us that you were a doctor?",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 is a doctor! Y'know what? Speaker 2'm just gonna go and talk to Rachel.",
      "Speaker 1: All right, Speaker 1 too. Should we wake Rachel up?",
      "Speaker 2: No! No, come on let Rachel sleep! Rachel's so exhausted."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "doctor",
        "rid": [
          29
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:title"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "baby",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Rachel",
        "y": "baby",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "baby",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Over here Jack. OK. Speaker 1 see, Rachel's coming up the path. Oh doesn't Rachel look pretty. Jack, get this.",
      "Speaker 2: Get a shot of Monica. Where's Monica.",
      "Speaker 3: Over here dad.",
      "Speaker 4: Wait, how do you zoom out? There Rachel is.",
      "Speaker 3: Oh, you look so great.",
      "Speaker 5: Ahh, so do you, beautiful.",
      "Speaker 3: Oops.",
      "Speaker 5: What?",
      "Speaker 3: Shoot, Speaker 3 think Speaker 3 got mayonaise on you.",
      "Speaker 5: Oh, that's OK, it's just the shoulder, it's not Speaker 5's dress.",
      "Speaker 4: Everybody smile.",
      "Speaker 3: Oh, Dad, turn it off.",
      "Speaker 4: It is off.",
      "Speaker 3: Dad, it is not. What's with the red light?",
      "Speaker 4: It's the red light. Right Ross?",
      "Speaker 6: You look pretty tonight.",
      "Speaker 5: Oh, thanks. So, uh, what are you gonna do this summer?",
      "Speaker 6: Oh, you know, Speaker 6'm just gonna, Speaker 6'm gonna hang out, work on Speaker 6's music.",
      "Speaker 5: Is Speaker 5's hook unhooked? These things keep falling down, Speaker 5 can't. . .",
      "Speaker 6: Uh, hold, let Speaker 6 see, Speaker 6 don't know. So what're you gonna do. . .",
      "Speaker 5: Oh, the guys are here.",
      "Speaker 6: this summer?"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 4",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "dad"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "beautiful",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "Jack",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "dad"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Alright, wait a second, why would Ross tell everyone in your class that you are as... \"gay as the day is long\"?",
      "Speaker 2: Because Speaker 2 told everyone Speaker 2 slept with dinosaurs.",
      "Speaker 1: But that's clearly a joke. This could easily be true.",
      "Speaker 2: Would you get that please? People have been calling to congratulate Speaker 2 all day.",
      "Speaker 1: Hello? No, he's not here. Yeah, this is he wife. Yeah, well, it came as quite a shock to Speaker 1 too. Speaker 1 guess Speaker 1 should have known. Yeah, Speaker 1 1 mean, Speaker 1 just kept making Speaker 1 watch Moulin Rouge.",
      "Speaker 2: Hang up, hang up. And that was a great movie! Speaker 2'm so gonna get back at Ross... oh yeah, this will show Ross, here we go.",
      "Speaker 1: What are you doing?",
      "Speaker 2: Oh, you'll see Speaker 2's friend."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "my friend",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
          "wife"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Ross",
        "rid": [
          4
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alumni"
        ],
        "t": [
          "class"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
          "wife"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Moulin Rouge",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "great movie"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "my friend",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Ross",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          4
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alumni"
        ],
        "t": [
          "class"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1'll just wait to put your order in.",
      "Speaker 2: You guys are over an hour late. What happened to you two?",
      "Speaker 3: Speaker 3'm so sorry ...",
      "Speaker 4: We got locked out of the apartment, we ...",
      "Speaker 5: That's a great story. Can Speaker 5 eat it?",
      "Speaker 3: And then Rachel wasn't sure Rachel could leave the baby.",
      "Speaker 4: It wasn't easy, but It's your birthday and Speaker 4 did what Speaker 4 got to do.",
      "Speaker 2: And that's Judy over there at the bar with Emma?",
      "Speaker 4: Oh honey, this is for the best, this way Speaker 4'm not distracted, worrying about Emma, how Speaker 4'm's doing at home and Speaker 4'm being completely here with you and, oh, Speaker 4'm spit up!",
      "Speaker 3: What?",
      "Speaker 4: Speaker 4'm spit up. Judy! Speaker 4'm spi...Judy! Look alive, Judy! Thank you.",
      "Speaker 3: Thanks. Oh.",
      "Speaker 3: Rach, c'mon, Emma is fine. You're turning into an obsessive mother. Okay, you need to stop.",
      "Speaker 4: You guys ever heard the story about when Ross's mom went to the beauty salon?",
      "Speaker 6: You mean the story about when Ross's mom went to the beauty salon?",
      "Speaker 3: Huh-huh, they already know the story about when Ross's mom went to the beauty salon!",
      "Speaker 2: You guys, we've been waiting for You guys for a long tiSpeaker 2, maybe you should order.",
      "Speaker 5: No, no, it's okay, Speaker 5 already told the waiter what they want.",
      "Speaker 7: Why would you do that?",
      "Speaker 5: Chandler, control your woman!",
      "Speaker 4: Okay, as everybody has ordered, Speaker 4 would like to start the celebration and make a toast ... to Phoebe. Phoebe dropped her sockock.",
      "Speaker 2: Aw ... what?",
      "Speaker 4: No, no, Emma dropped her sockk.",
      "Speaker 7: Mom's here? Speaker 7 wanted to have lunch with Emma today, Emma told Speaker 7 Emma was out of town.",
      "Speaker 4: Ross, Ross still has not noticed that her sock is on the ground.",
      "Speaker 2: It's a good toast.",
      "Speaker 4: Could you please get Emma attention?",
      "Speaker 3: Mommy!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "honey",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "Rach",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "Emma",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "mother"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "honey",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "Mommy",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Judy",
        "y": "Mommy",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Judy",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "Mommy"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Judy",
        "y": "Speaker 7",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "Mom"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Judy",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "Mommy"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 7",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "honey",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 7",
        "y": "Judy",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "Mom"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 7",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 7",
        "y": "honey",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Emma",
        "y": "Speaker 4",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "mother"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 5",
        "y": "honey",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 6",
        "y": "honey",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hi!",
      "Speaker 2: Hey! So what's the big news you had us rush all the way over here for?",
      "Speaker 3: Okay, us news. Speaker 3's company has asked Speaker 3 to head up us office in Tulsa , so as of Monday Speaker 3'm being officially relocated.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh Speaker 2's God!",
      "Speaker 4: What?!",
      "Speaker 1: What?!",
      "Speaker 2: Monday?!",
      "Speaker 5: How long do you have to go for?",
      "Speaker 3: They said it could be up to a year.",
      "Speaker 5: A year?!",
      "Speaker 1: Do you have to go?",
      "Speaker 6: Speaker 6 kind of have to don't Speaker 6? Because of this stupid thing.",
      "Speaker 3: There is nothing like the support of your loving wife, huh?",
      "Speaker 5: Wait a minute, you can't go to Tulsa. Maybe you forgot, but we've got tickets to the Jets game next week.",
      "Speaker 3: Speaker 3'm sorry buddy, but Speaker 3 don't think Speaker 3'm gonna be able to make it.",
      "Speaker 5: We were gonna go see the Jets!",
      "Speaker 2: You can't go, Speaker 2 mean you're the glue that holds this group together!",
      "Speaker 3: Really?",
      "Speaker 2: Not you.",
      "Speaker 5: Speaker 5 can't believe you guys are moving.",
      "Speaker 4: Speaker 4 call you guys apartment!!!",
      "Speaker 7: No!!! Ah!! Ahh!!!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 6",
        "rid": [
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
          "wife"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "buddy",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 6",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
          "wife"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 6",
        "y": "glue",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 5",
        "y": "buddy",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 5",
        "y": "Jets",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "buddy",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 don't know what else to say.",
      "Speaker 2: Well that works out good, because Speaker 2'm not listening.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 feel terrible, Speaker 1 really do.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh, Speaker 2'm sorry, did Speaker 2's back hurt your knife?",
      "Speaker 1: Rachel, say that Speaker 1'm friends with Rachel, we spend some time together. Is that so terrible?",
      "Speaker 2: Yes.",
      "Speaker 1: It's that terrible?",
      "Speaker 2: Yes. Monica, you don't get it. It's bad enough that Monica's stolen the guy who might actually be the person that Speaker 2 is supposed to be with, but now, Monica's actually, but now Monica's actually stealing you.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1? What are you talking about? Nobody could steal Speaker 1 from Rachel. Speaker 1 mean, just because Speaker 2'm friends with Monica doesn't make Speaker 1 any less friends with Rachel. Speaker 1 mean, you're my...We're, we're...Oh, Speaker 1 love you.",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 love you too.",
      "Speaker 3: You guys, um Speaker 3 know that this really doesn't have anything to do with Speaker 3, but um Speaker 3 love you guys too. Oh, Speaker 3 really needed that.",
      "Speaker 1: Look, Speaker 1 know that you're in a place right now where you really need to hate Julie's guts, but Julie didn't do anything wrong. Speaker 1 mean, Julie was just a girl who met a guy, and now they go out. Speaker 1 really think that if you gave Julie a chance, you'd like Julie. Would you just give that a chance, for Speaker 1?",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 3 do anything for you, you know that.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1'd do anything for you.",
      "Speaker 3: Wait, wait, wait, wait!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          9,
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:friends",
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "friends",
          "love"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Julie",
        "rid": [
          9
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:friends"
        ],
        "t": [
          "friends with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          1,
          9
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression",
          "per:friends"
        ],
        "t": [
          "love you",
          "friends"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "love you guys"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "love you guys"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Julie",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          9
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:friends"
        ],
        "t": [
          "friends with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hey buddy.",
      "Speaker 2: Uh, hi.",
      "Speaker 1: Um, can Speaker 1 come back in?",
      "Speaker 2: Why?",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1, Speaker 1 was just thinking about how much more we have to talk about.",
      "Speaker 2: But you left."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "buddy",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          2
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:negative_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hi, it's Speaker 1.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh, my, god.",
      "Speaker 3: Janice? You called Janice?",
      "Speaker 1: Yes, Janice. Why is that so difficult for you to comprehend?",
      "Speaker 4: You remember Janice, right?",
      "Speaker 1: Yes. Janice was smart, Janice was pretty, and Janice honestly cared about Speaker 1. Janice is Speaker 1's last chance to have somebody.",
      "Speaker 2: Helloo!!",
      "Speaker 1: Oh, my, god!",
      "Speaker 5: Geez, look how fat Janice got.",
      "Speaker 2: Hey, it's everybody.",
      "Speaker 1: Janice, you're--",
      "Speaker 2: Yes, Speaker 2 am.",
      "Speaker 1: Is it--?",
      "Speaker 2: Is it yours? Ha! You wish, Chandler Bing. You are looking at a married lady now.",
      "Speaker 1: Congratulations.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh, sweetie, Speaker 2 sorry.",
      "Speaker 1: You couldn't have told Speaker 1 about this on the phone?",
      "Speaker 2: And what? Missed the expression on your face? Janice likes to have Janice fun."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "cared about"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Chandler Bing",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "sweetie",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 4",
        "y": "sweetie",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 5",
        "y": "sweetie",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "sweetie",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "sweetie",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Yo, paisan! Can Speaker 1 talk to you for a sec? Your tailor is a very bad man!",
      "Speaker 2: Frankie? What're you talking about?",
      "Speaker 3: Hey, what's goin' on?",
      "Speaker 1: Joey's tailor...took advantage of Speaker 1.",
      "Speaker 3: What?",
      "Speaker 2: No way. Speaker 2've been going to the guy for 12 years."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "paisan",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Frankie",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          7
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:client"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Frankie",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          7
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:client"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Frankie",
        "y": "tailor",
        "rid": [
          29
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:title"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Frankie",
        "rid": [
          2
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:negative_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "man",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "man",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "man",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Eddie, Speaker 1 didn't sleep with your ex-girlfriend.",
      "Speaker 2: That's very interesting, ya know, 'cause that's exactly what someone who slept with her would say.",
      "Speaker 1: This is nuts. This is crazy. her came over for like two minutes, dropped off a fish tank, and left, end of story.",
      "Speaker 2: Where's Buddy?",
      "Speaker 1: Buddy?",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2's fish, Buddy.",
      "Speaker 1: There was no fish when her dropped no fish off.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh, this is, this is unbelievable. Speaker 2 mean, first you sleep with Speaker 2's ex-girlfriend then you insult Speaker 2's intelligence by lying about it and then you kill Speaker 2's fish, Speaker 2's Buddy?",
      "Speaker 1: Hey Speaker 1 didn't kill Speaker 2's fish. Look Eddie... Would you look at what Speaker 1 1'm doin' here. That can't be smart. So we're just gonna take this guy right off ya and put this guy here in Mr. Pocket. Tangellon?"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Buddy",
        "rid": [
          31
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:pet"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Buddy",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Okay, now the Mastodon is from the semi-late Jurassic period.",
      "Speaker 2: Isn't the Mastodon from the Pliocene Epic?",
      "Speaker 1: Shhh! This is a museum, no talking. Right down here,  Uhh, and over here we have Ross Geller. Everyone wave 'Hi' to Ross. Ross is one of we most important scientists, look at Ross, hard at work. Okay, moving right along. Come on."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Ross Geller",
        "y": "scientist",
        "rid": [
          29
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:title"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Ross Geller",
        "y": "museum",
        "rid": [
          28
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:place_of_work"
        ],
        "t": [
          "at work"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "museum",
        "rid": [
          28
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:place_of_work"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Ross Geller",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Monica, why don't you finish off these pies? Speaker 1 don't have any more room left in the fridge.",
      "Speaker 2: No. No, thank you!",
      "Speaker 3: Well Judy, you did it! Judy's finally full!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Judy",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Judy",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 have sex with dinosaurs??",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 believe Speaker 2 read that somewhere!",
      "Speaker 1: That only is not funny, it's physically impossible! Ok? Depending on the species Speaker 1'd have to have a six foot long... It's not funny!!",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 respectfully disagree.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 can't believe you put that on Speaker 1's alumni page!",
      "Speaker 2: Who cares? Nobody reads those things",
      "Speaker 1: You'd better hope not because Speaker 1 just read what you put on your page today.",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 don't have a page.",
      "Speaker 1: Oh oh oh! Speaker 1 RESPECTFULLY DISAGREE!!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          4
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alumni"
        ],
        "t": [
          "alumni"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          4
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alumni"
        ],
        "t": [
          "alumni"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Good morning!",
      "Speaker 2: Hello. But you know what, hey, new day, new leaf, Speaker 2 is just really really happy ... Speaker 2'm sorry, obviously Heather's ass has something more important to say so Speaker 2'll just wait 'till it's finished.",
      "Speaker 3: What?",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 was giving you an apology and you were totally checking Speaker 2 out!",
      "Speaker 3: Speaker 3 wasn't checking Speaker 2 out. Speaker 3'm in fashion, Speaker 3 was looking at Speaker 2 skirt. Or was it pants? Speaker 3 didn't really see what happened below the ass area.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh wow, you are really, you're really a creep.",
      "Speaker 3: Why do you even care if Speaker 3 was looking at Speaker 2? Are you jealous?",
      "Speaker 2: Oh yeah, Speaker 3. \"Oh Gavin, please, please look at Speaker 2's ass\". Stop looking at Speaker 2's ass! Speaker 2 mean, Speaker 2 just think you are totally inappropriate, ok? This is a work environment, Speaker 2's your subordinate.",
      "Speaker 3: Speaker 3 thought it was ok when you slept with your old assistant Tag.",
      "Speaker 2: That is totally different for two reasons. One - Speaker 2 didn't know that you knew that. And two, Speaker 2 wasn't some creep staring at Speaker 2's ass 2 ass, we had a deep meaningful relationship.",
      "Speaker 3: Huh. What's your old assistant Tag's last naSpeaker 3?",
      "Speaker 2: It was ... oh Speaker 2's god. Speaker 2 didn't have a last naSpeaker 2. It was just \"Tag\". You know, like Cher, or, you know, Moses.",
      "Speaker 3: But it was a deep meaningful relationship.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh, you know what - Speaker 2's first impression of you was absolutely right. You are arrogant, you are pompous ... Morgan! Morgan! your old assistant Tag's last name was Morgan! Huh!",
      "Speaker 3: It was Jones.",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah well what are you, Speaker 2 boyfriend?"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Tag",
        "y": "Jones",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Tag",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          10,
          5
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend",
          "per:boss"
        ],
        "t": [
          "a deep meaningful relationship",
          "assistant"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Tag",
        "y": "assistant",
        "rid": [
          29
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:title"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          2
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:negative_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "arrogant"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Tag",
        "rid": [
          10,
          6
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend",
          "per:subordinate"
        ],
        "t": [
          "a deep meaningful relationship",
          "assistant"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          5
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:boss"
        ],
        "t": [
          "subordinate"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "a creep",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          6
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:subordinate"
        ],
        "t": [
          "subordinate"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: You want Speaker 1 to see a therapist?",
      "Speaker 2: Sweetheart, you obviously have a problem. You've chosen a boyfriend exactly like your father.",
      "Speaker 1: Ok mom, you know what, fine, Speaker 1'll make an appointment ok, but you know what, right now, Speaker 1 gotta go, Speaker 1 gotta go do a thing.",
      "Speaker 3: Did you know your mother spent $1200 dollars on bansai trees. Speaker 3 felt like Gulliver around that place.",
      "Speaker 1: Daddy, daddy, you know what, Speaker 1 really wanna hear more about this, Speaker 1 really do, but Speaker 1 just have, Speaker 1 just have to do a, some stuff.",
      "Speaker 4: Ok, ok, you can be shirts and Speaker 4'll be skins. Speaker 4'll be skins. Hey, how you holdin' up there, tiger? Oh, sorry, when Speaker 4's parents were getting divorced Speaker 4 got a lot of tigers. Got a lot of champs, chiefs, sports, Speaker 4 even got a governor.",
      "Speaker 1: This is it, isn't it? Speaker 1 mean, this is what Speaker 1's life is gonna be like. Speaker 1's mom there, Speaker 1's dad there. Thanksgiving, Christmas. Speaker 1's dad there gets the house, Speaker 1's dad there's in some condo Speaker 1's sister's gonna decorate with wicker. Oh, Chandler how did you get through this?",
      "Speaker 4: Well, Speaker 4 relied on a carefully regimented program of denial and, and wetting the bed.",
      "Speaker 1: Ya know, Speaker 1 just, so weird. Speaker 1 mean Speaker 1 was in there just listening to them bitch about each other and all Speaker 1 kept thinking about was the fourth of July.",
      "Speaker 4: Because it reminded you of the way our forefathers used to bitch at each other?",
      "Speaker 1: It's just this thing. Every year we would go out on Speaker 1's dad's boat and watch the fireworks. Mom always hated it because the ocean air made Mom hair all big. Speaker 1's sister Jill would be throwing up over the side and Speaker 1's dad would be upset because nobody was helping and then when we did help Speaker 1's sister Jill would scream at us for doing it wrong. But then when the fireworks started, everybody just shut up, you know, and it'd get really cold, and we would all just sort of smush under this one blanket. it never occured to anybody to bring another one. And now it's just...",
      "Speaker 4: Speaker 4, Speaker 4 know."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "mom"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "sweetheart",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "daddy"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Jill",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          "sister"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
          "getting divorced"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "daddy"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Jill",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "dad"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Jill",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "mom"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Jill",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "dad"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Jill",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          "sister"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "mom"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
          "getting divorced"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Jill",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "mom"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "bitch",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Okay, you come up with an idea.",
      "Speaker 2: Alright alright, we still have three hours till escrow closes on our house We can still get out.",
      "Speaker 1: But we love our house",
      "Speaker 2: Will we love our house so much with her next door? And her's gonna be louder out here too. Just the crickets and \"Oh Speaker 2's God\"!",
      "Speaker 1: Okay, but if we don't get our house, her's stil gonna show up wherever we go! Speaker 1 mean, at least if her's here, it eliminates the element of surprise. Speaker 1 mean, never again will you have to hear the three words that make your balls jump back up inside your body.",
      "Speaker 2: Well, we have to do something. We can't have her living next door. Oh, that does it too.",
      "Speaker 3: Well... Speaker 3 just talked to Sid, we are definitely putting in an offer on our house... a-a-and Speaker 3'll bet we get it.",
      "Speaker 2: The Hitlers will be so disappointed.",
      "Speaker 3: All right, Speaker 3 got to run. Tell Monica Speaker 3 say goodbye. And... Speaker 3 see you later, neighbor.",
      "Speaker 2: Wait! Speaker 2 just want you to know that... Speaker 3 so happy you're going to be here.",
      "Speaker 3: Oh, Speaker 3 too...",
      "Speaker 2: Because... that way... we can pick up where we left off.",
      "Speaker 3: Huh?",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 never stopped loving you.",
      "Speaker 3: Oh... my...",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah, yeah, yeah! Speaker 2 want you... Speaker 2 need you... Speaker 2 must have you Janice Litman Goralnik Neihosenstein.",
      "Speaker 3: Chandler, what are you talking about?",
      "Speaker 2: Now that you live next door, we can be together every day. Sid and Monica never have to know a thing.",
      "Speaker 3: Speaker 3 don't know what to say... Speaker 3 mean, you know, obviously we have this... heat between us.",
      "Speaker 2: Obviously.",
      "Speaker 3: But Speaker 3 love Speaker 3's husband. And Speaker 3 know you love your wife. Now, Speaker 3 don't think we should get this house now.",
      "Speaker 2: Don't say that. Don't tangle the dream and take the dream away.",
      "Speaker 3: Chandler, one of us has got to be strong.",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 understand.",
      "Speaker 3: Although, maybe just... one last moment of weakness... Goodbye Chandler Bing.",
      "Speaker 2: They're never coming down now."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          10,
          2
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend",
          "per:negative_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "pick up where we left off",
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Chandler Bing",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "neighbor",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
          "wife"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "pick up where we left off"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Janice Litman Goralnik Neihosenstein",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Sid",
        "rid": [
          17,
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse",
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "husband",
          "love"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          2
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:negative_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
          "wife"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Sid",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
          "husband"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hey Chandler! Saw the new furniture. Very nice.",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah! Joey has the best boyfriend ever!",
      "Speaker 3: Speaker 3 kissed Kathy.",
      "Speaker 1: What?",
      "Speaker 2: Are you serious?",
      "Speaker 4: Does Joey know?",
      "Speaker 3: No. Is there anyway, anyway you think Joey'll understand this?",
      "Speaker 2: You obviously haven't screwed over a lot of your friends. Which we all appreciate.",
      "Speaker 1: No the-the sad thing is, if you had told Joey how you felt before you kissed her, knowing Joey, Joey probably just would've just stepped aside.",
      "Speaker 3: Oh, don't say that! Don't say that. That's not true. Is it?",
      "Speaker 4: Speaker 4 think maybe, yeah.",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 loves you.",
      "Speaker 3: Then why didn't you tell Speaker 3 to do that?!!",
      "Speaker 1: Well, Speaker 1 said-I said something to Phoebe.",
      "Speaker 4: Yeah! No, that's right. And Speaker 4 thought it was a really good idea.",
      "Speaker 5: Speaker 5 know, Speaker 5 remember that!",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 remember you did.",
      "Speaker 3: God!! What is Speaker 3 gonna do?!",
      "Speaker 5: Well, Chandler, you're gonna have to tell Chandler.",
      "Speaker 3: Why?! Why do Speaker 3 have to tell Chandler?!",
      "Speaker 5: Because you do.",
      "Speaker 3: Yeah, Speaker 3 know.",
      "Speaker 1: Hey, would it be okay if Speaker 1 wrote a song about this."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Joey",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          9,
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:friends",
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "boyfriend",
          "loves"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Joey",
        "rid": [
          9
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:friends"
        ],
        "t": [
          "boyfriend"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Kathy",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: All right, Speaker 1 have one question. What is the deal with this?",
      "Speaker 2: Bye-bye little puppet Joey hand?",
      "Speaker 1: No, the quiet down thing!",
      "Speaker 2: You mean this.",
      "Speaker 1: Um-hmm! Look, Speaker 1-Speaker 1-I don't know how much more of this Speaker 1 can take! Did you know he taped over Speaker 1's Baywatch tape with some show about bugs! Speaker 1's God! What if that had been porn?",
      "Speaker 2: All right look, y'know, this maybe tough but come on, this is Ross! Speaker 2 survived college with Speaker 2!",
      "Speaker 1: All right, Speaker 1 guess Speaker 1 can hold out a little longer. Let's have a gaSpeaker 1.",
      "Speaker 2: Okay."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Ross",
        "rid": [
          4
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alumni"
        ],
        "t": [
          "survived college with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Ross",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          4
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alumni"
        ],
        "t": [
          "survived college with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hey guys! Hey!",
      "Speaker 2: Hey Pheebs, guess who we saw today.",
      "Speaker 3: Ooh, ooh, fun! Okay... um, Liam Neeson.",
      "Speaker 2: Nope.",
      "Speaker 3: Morly Safer.",
      "Speaker 2: Nope.",
      "Speaker 3: The woman who cuts Speaker 3's hair!",
      "Speaker 4: Okay, look, this could be a really long gaSpeaker 4.",
      "Speaker 5: Your sister Ursula.",
      "Speaker 3: Oh, really.",
      "Speaker 5: Yeah, yeah, Your sister Ursula.",
      " works over at that place, uh...",
      "Speaker 3: Rift's. Yeah, Speaker 3 know.",
      "Speaker 5: Oh, you do? Because Your sister Ursula.",
      " said you guys haven't talked in like years.",
      "Speaker 3: Hmmm? Yeah. So, um, is Your sister Ursula.",
      " fat?",
      "Speaker 2: Not from where Speaker 2 was standin'.",
      "Speaker 3:  where were you standing?",
      "Speaker 6: Um, Pheebs, so, you guys just don't get along?",
      "Speaker 3: It's mostly just dumb sister stuff, you know, Speaker 3 mean, like, everyone always thought of Your sister Ursula.",
      " as the pretty one, you know... Oh, oh, Your sister Ursula.",
      " was the first one to start walking, even though Speaker 3 did it... later that same day. But, to Speaker 3's parents, by then it was like \"yeah, right, well what else is new?\""
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Pheebs",
        "y": "Ursula",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          "sister"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Pheebs",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Ursula",
        "rid": [
          2
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:negative_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Ursula",
        "y": "Rift’s",
        "rid": [
          22
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:employee_or_member_of"
        ],
        "t": [
          "works over at"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "x": "Ursula",
        "y": "Pheebs",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          "sister"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 6",
        "y": "Pheebs",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Rift’s",
        "y": "Ursula",
        "rid": [
          35
        ],
        "r": [
          "org:employees_or_members"
        ],
        "t": [
          "works over at"
        ],
        "x_type": "ORG",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hi!",
      "Speaker 2: Hi.",
      "Speaker 1: Oh, Speaker 1'm so glad you called. Speaker 1 feel like it's always Speaker 1 calling you. So, what's up? Is everything okay with Phoebe?",
      "Speaker 2: It will be…in a minute. Listen, Tim you're a really great guy.",
      "Speaker 1: It's because Speaker 1'm with you.",
      "Speaker 2: Aw. Speaker 2'm just—Speaker 2'm in a place in Speaker 2's life right now where Speaker 2…Speaker 2…",
      "Speaker 1: Whoops. Sorry. This just in. Oh, it's 9-1-1 from the restaurant, that means Monica needs Speaker 1 right away.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh-oh no Phoebe doesn't! Speaker 2 know what that is. You can stay.",
      "Speaker 1: Awww, Speaker 1'll miss you too Pheebs. And Speaker 1 will be holding you, right here."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          1,
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression",
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "",
          "with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Pheebs",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hey guys.",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 3, Speaker 4: Hey.",
      "Speaker 2: What's in the bag?",
      "Speaker 1: Um, just some presents.",
      "Speaker 4: C'mon show us what you bought. . . You know you want to.",
      "Speaker 1: OK. OK, this is a picture frame from Ben to Speaker 1's parents, huh.",
      "Speaker 3: Cute.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 got soSpeaker 1, uh, hers and hers towels for Susan and Carol. And, uh, Speaker 1 got this blouse for mom.",
      "Speaker 3: Ross, that is gorgeous!",
      "Speaker 1: Yeah?",
      "Speaker 3: Look at these authentic fake medals. Speaker 3 tell ya, mom's gonna be voted best dressed at the make-believe military academy."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Susan",
        "y": "Carol",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "hers and hers"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          16
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:siblings"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Carol",
        "y": "Susan",
        "rid": [
          10
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend"
        ],
        "t": [
          "hers and hers"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Ross.",
      "Speaker 2: Yeah?",
      "Speaker 1: Can Speaker 1 ask you something?",
      "Speaker 2: Uh-huh.",
      "Speaker 1: When Carol was pregnant with Ben…",
      "Speaker 2: Mmm?",
      "Speaker 1: …were you this irritating?",
      "Speaker 2: Wow!",
      "Speaker 1: Excuse Speaker 1?!",
      "Speaker 2: Oh nothing. Nothing! Just uh, you've been a little short with Speaker 2 lately. Speaker 2 not trying to irritate you.",
      "Speaker 1: Well then you just must have a natural talent for it.",
      "Speaker 2: Y'know what? The doctor will be in soon, why don't we not speak until then.",
      "Speaker 1: Okay. Seriously, breathe louder Ross! That's great!",
      "Speaker 2: Y'know we should probably ask The doctor if The doctor even knows how to deliver a baby that's half human and half pure evil!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Carol",
        "y": "Ben",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "pregnant with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Ben",
        "y": "Carol",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          "pregnant with"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hey, Lizzie.",
      "Speaker 2: Hey, Weird Girl.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 brought you alphabet soup.",
      "Speaker 2: Did you pick out the vowels?",
      "Speaker 1: Yes. But Speaker 1 left in the Ys. 'Cause, y'know, \"sometimes y\". Uh, Speaker 1 also have something else for you.",
      "Speaker 2: Saltines?",
      "Speaker 1: No, but would you like a thousand dollars and a football phone?",
      "Speaker 2: What? Oh Speaker 2's God, there's really money in here.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 know.",
      "Speaker 2: Weird Girl, what are you doing?",
      "Speaker 1: No, Speaker 1 want you to have it. Speaker 1 don't want it.",
      "Speaker 2: No, no, Speaker 2 ha-I have to give you something.",
      "Speaker 1: Oh, that's fine, no.",
      "Speaker 2: Would you like Speaker 2's tin-foil hat?",
      "Speaker 1: No. 'Cause you need that. No, it's okay, thanks.",
      "Speaker 2: Please, let Speaker 2 do something.",
      "Speaker 1: Okay, alright, you buy Speaker 1 a soda, and then we're even. Okay?",
      "Speaker 2: Okay.",
      "Speaker 1: Okay."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Weird Girl",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          3
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:acquaintance"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          3
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:acquaintance"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Okay... aahhh... Please laugh for mommy... Please? Please laugh for mommy... Not funny huh? Oh so, is it... only offensive novelty rap? Or maybe just, you know, rap in general? 'Cause mommy can rap... Speaker 1's name is mommy and Speaker 1'm here to say / that all the babies are... Oh, Speaker 1 can't rap... All right sweetheart... This is only because Speaker 1 love you so much, and Speaker 1 know that you're not gonna tell anybody... Speaker 1 like... big butts and Speaker 1 cannot lie... / You other brothers can't deny... / when a girl walks in with an itty bitty waist and a round thing in your face... Yes! Yes! Yes! YES! Oohhhhh! Oh!  Speaker 1 like big butts and Speaker 1 cannot lie... / You other brothers can't deny... Oh Emma you're laughing! Oh you are, you really do like big butts, don't you. Oh you beautiful little weirdo...",
      "Speaker 2: Hey!",
      "Speaker 1: Oh you missed it. She was laughing. Oh it was amazing. It was amazing. It was the most beautiful, beautiful sound that...",
      "Speaker 2: Oh Speaker 2 know, isn't it? Ooh... what'd you do to get She to laugh?",
      "Speaker 1: Oh! You know, Speaker 1 just... couple of things Speaker 1 tried ... Speaker 1 just sang a little doo... Itsy Bitsy Spider...",
      "Speaker 2: You sang Baby Got Back didn't you?",
      "Speaker 1: Nothing else worked. She is all about the ass..."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "mommy",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Emma",
        "rid": [
          13,
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children",
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "mommy",
          "love"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "sweetheart",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Emma",
        "y": "sweetheart",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Emma",
        "y": "beautiful little weirdo",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Emma",
        "y": "Baby Got Back",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Emma",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          "mommy"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Baby",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "sweetheart",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Dr. Geller, Sherman Whitfield, London Institute.",
      "Speaker 2: Wow! What a pleasure.",
      "Speaker 3: Well, Speaker 3 have to tell you, Speaker 3 was quite impressed with your paper on Pre-Cretaceous fossils. Yeah, your paper on Pre-Cretaceous fossils confirmed everything that Speaker 3 have written.",
      "Speaker 4: Excuse Speaker 4. Hi.",
      "Speaker 3: Yes?",
      "Speaker 4: Well, your kind of sitting in Speaker 4's seat.",
      "Speaker 3: What do you mean, your seat?",
      "Speaker 4: Speaker 4 mean, Speaker 4 was sitting there.",
      "Speaker 3: But, you got up!",
      "Speaker 4: But, Speaker 4 never left the room!",
      "Speaker 3: But, you left the chair area.",
      "Speaker 4: All right, that's it, give Speaker 4 your underwear."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "London Institute",
        "rid": [
          22
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:employee_or_member_of"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "ORG"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Dr. Geller",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "London Institute",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          35
        ],
        "r": [
          "org:employees_or_members"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "ORG",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Hey.",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 3: Hey.",
      "Speaker 1: Is ah, is Chandler around?",
      "Speaker 3: No, umm, Chandler met some girl at the coffee house.",
      "Speaker 1: Oooh.",
      "Speaker 3: Yeah, Ginger something.",
      "Speaker 1: Nooo. No, no, ah, are you sure it wasn't something that sounded like Ginger, like ah, Gingeer?",
      "Speaker 3: No, it was Ginger. Speaker 3 remember, because when Chandler told Speaker 3, Speaker 3 said, 'the movie star.'",
      "Speaker 1: Aww, man. That's the girl Speaker 1 was hiding from. When the movie star finds out Chandler's Speaker 1's roommate, the movie star's gonna tell Chandler what Speaker 1 did.",
      "Speaker 3: Well, what did you do?",
      "Speaker 1: What, oh, oh, oh, no, no, Speaker 1 can't, Speaker 1 can't tell you that, it's like the most awful, horrible thing Speaker 1've ever done Speaker 1's whole life.",
      "Speaker 3: Y'know what, don't tell us. We'll just wait until Chandler around gets hoSpeaker 3, because it'll be more fun that way.",
      "Speaker 1: All right!! Okay, it was like four years ago. Okay, Ginger and Speaker 1 had gone out a few times, and then this one weekend, we went up to the movie star Dad's cabin. Just Speaker 1, the movie star, and the movie star annoying little dog Pepper. Well that night, Speaker 1 cooked this really romantic dinner....",
      "Speaker 3: You gave the movie star food poisoning!?",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 wish. No. After dinner, Speaker 1, the movie star, and Pepper all fell asleep in front of the fire. Well Speaker 1 woke up in the middle of the night and Speaker 1 saw that the fire was dying out. So, Speaker 1 picked up a log and threw a log on. Or, at least what Speaker 1 thought was a log.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh Speaker 2's God!! You threw Pepper on the fire!",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 wish. See, Speaker 1 guess another thing Speaker 1 probably should've told you about Ginger is that Gingernda has a ah, artificial leg.",
      "Speaker 3: Oh Speaker 3's God! Joey, what did you do after you threw Joey leg on the fire?",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 ran!!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Chandler",
        "rid": [
          12
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:roommate"
        ],
        "t": [
          "roommate"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "man",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Dad",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "girl",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Ginger",
        "y": "Pepper",
        "rid": [
          31
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:pet"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Chandler",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          12
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:roommate"
        ],
        "t": [
          "roommate"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Chandler",
        "y": "man",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 3",
        "y": "man",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "man",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Oh hey Ross, oh Speaker 1'm so glad someone's here. Could you zip Speaker 1 up?",
      "Speaker 2: Sure.",
      "Speaker 1: Thank you. Can you believe no one between Speaker 1's apartment and here offered to do that for Speaker 1?.",
      "Speaker 2: People. So why you all dressed up?",
      "Speaker 1: Oh umm. Mike's picking Speaker 1 up for a date.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh yea? Now um, how is that going, is it getting serious?",
      "Speaker 1: Oh Speaker 1 dunno, Speaker 1 dunno, you know Speaker 1 mean, Speaker 1 like Mike but is Speaker 1 ready to take Speaker 1's grade-A loins off the meat market?",
      "Speaker 2: You know, Speaker 2 really admire your whole dating attitude, it's so healthy. Speaker 2'm always like, is this moving to fast? Is this moving to slow? Where's this going?",
      "Speaker 1: Yeah, you know, you are a bit of a drama queen.",
      "Speaker 2: But you, you're so much better off. You just go from guy to guy having fun and never worrying that it terms into anything serious.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 wouldn't say never, you know. There's guy ... well what about...OK well there's gotta be someone.",
      "Speaker 2: There isn't. That's what Speaker 2'm saying.",
      "Speaker 1: Oh Speaker 1's God, you're right!",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 know, and yet here you are, all ready for the next date.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 can't believe Speaker 1 never realized this before. Speaker 1'm in Speaker 1's 30s and never been in a long-term relationship! Oh Speaker 1's God! What's wrong with Speaker 1?",
      "Speaker 2: No, no, no there's nothing wrong with you. Speaker 2 mean, you don't strike Speaker 2 as the type of person that wants to get married anyway.",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 wanna get married!",
      "Speaker 2: Please don't cry because of Speaker 2, Pheebs. Speaker 2 don't know what Speaker 2'm talking about. Speaker 2've been divorced three times!",
      "Speaker 1: At least you've been married! Oh Speaker 1's God! Speaker 1 wanna trade lives with Ross!"
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Pheebs",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Mike",
        "rid": [
          8,
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:dates",
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "",
          "like"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "drama queen",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Mike",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          8
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:dates"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Isn't it incredible?! Monica and Chandler, gettin' married.",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 know, Monica and Chandler, gettin''re gonna be so happy together.",
      "Speaker 1: Ohh… Speaker 1 mean two best friends falling in love, how often does that happen?",
      "Speaker 2: Not that often!",
      "Speaker 1: No! Speaker 1'm so happy for Monica and Chandler, gettin'!",
      "Speaker 2: Speaker 2 too! So happy for Monica and Chandler, gettin'!",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1'm so happy and not at all jealous.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh no! No God, definitely not jealous!",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 mean Speaker 1'm probably 98% happy, maybe 2% jealous. And Speaker 1 mean what's 2%? That's nothing.",
      "Speaker 2: Totally. Speaker 2'm like 90/10.",
      "Speaker 1: Yeah Speaker 1 too."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Monica",
        "y": "Chandler",
        "rid": [
          10,
          9
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend",
          "per:friends"
        ],
        "t": [
          "falling in love",
          "best friends"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Chandler",
        "y": "Monica",
        "rid": [
          10,
          9
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:girl/boyfriend",
          "per:friends"
        ],
        "t": [
          "falling in love",
          "best friends"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Look at that face! Just like when you were in high school! If Speaker 1 didn't know better Speaker 1'd say you were a cheerleader in trouble. Come on, let's get some tea.",
      "Speaker 2: Okay.",
      "Speaker 1: Oh Speaker 1's look at that. Only three weeks to go, now have you picked your nanny yet? Now Speaker 1 don't want you to use your housekeeper 'cause it would just split your housekeeper focus.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh well actually gonna use a nanny and uh, Speaker 2 don't even have a housekeeper.",
      "Speaker 1: It's like you're a cave person. Rachel, you must get a nanny. You don't know how overwhelming this is going to be. Speaker 1 mean when you were a baby Speaker 1 had full time help, Speaker 1 had Mrs. Kay.",
      "Speaker 2: Mrs. Kay! Oh yeah, Rachel was sweet. Rachel taught Speaker 2 Spanish. Speaker 2 actually think Speaker 2 remember some of Speaker 2, tu madre es loca.",
      "Speaker 1: Such a sweet woman.",
      "Speaker 2: Well, however great Rachel was Speaker 2 just can't afford that.",
      "Speaker 1: Oh Rachel!",
      "Speaker 2: What?",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1 just had the greatest idea! Speaker 1'm gonna come live with Rachel!",
      "Speaker 2: Wh-wh-what? What?",
      "Speaker 1: Oh, Speaker 1'm so happy Speaker 1'm gonna do this for Speaker 1's little girl. Aw, look at Rachel. You have tears in your eyes.",
      "Speaker 2: Yes. Yes Speaker 2 do."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Mrs. Kay",
        "y": "nanny",
        "rid": [
          29
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:title"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Mrs. Kay",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "sweet"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "little girl",
        "rid": [
          30
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:alternate_names"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "Speaker 1",
        "rid": [
          15
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:parents"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 2",
        "y": "baby",
        "rid": [
          37
        ],
        "r": [
          "unanswerable"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "STRING"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Mrs. Kay",
        "rid": [
          1
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:positive_impression"
        ],
        "t": [
          "sweet"
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      },
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 2",
        "rid": [
          13
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:children"
        ],
        "t": [
          ""
        ],
        "x_type": "PER",
        "y_type": "PER"
      }
    ]
  ],
  [
    [
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1'm not here! That's just Speaker 1's Chinese food!",
      "Speaker 2: Oh, Speaker 2's God! She has food delivered here?",
      "Speaker 3: Mm-hmm. She's—She's emotional, but, but ballsy.",
      "Speaker 1: You know what Speaker 1'm going to do? Speaker 1'm going to get in Speaker 1's sweats, and eat this in bed!",
      "Speaker 3: And you thought She was going to be in our way! So, why don't you, uh, open the champagne, and Speaker 1'm be right back. Speaker 3've got a surprise for you.",
      "Speaker 2: You got another ex-wife back there?",
      "Speaker 3: Please start drinking!",
      "Speaker 1: Speaker 1'm just going to grab the phone.",
      "Speaker 2: Oh, Rachel! Wait! Hey, Speaker 2 hope you don't take this the wrong way, but, but, um… what are you doing?",
      "Speaker 1: Oh, Speaker 1'm sorry! Do you need the phone?",
      "Speaker 2: No, no. Listen, Ross is too nice to say anything, but this is Ross apartment, and, and, we gotta have some boundaries, so why don't you go back to your place and give us some privacy?",
      "Speaker 1: But, but, Mona, Speaker 1 live here.",
      "Speaker 3: Happy Valentine's Day! …Or something to remember Speaker 3 by."
    ],
    [
      {
        "x": "Speaker 1",
        "y": "Speaker 3",
        "rid": [
          12,
          17
        ],
        "r": [
          "per:roommate",
          "per:spouse"
        ],
        "t": [
